15five.com 2019-12-20

# Privacy Policy - 15Five

15Five, Inc. (“15Five,” “we” or “us”) is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how 15Five collects, uses, and shares the personal information we collect from visitors to our website (“Website”). For information about how we collect and use information collected from our customers during the provision of our service (“Service”), please see “Information Gathering and Usage,” below. By accessing or using our Service, you signify that you have read, understood and agree to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We collect personal information about you from various sources to provide our services to you, to analyze and improve our services, and to communicate with you. To help you understand how we use and share this information, this Privacy Policy describes our data privacy and confidentiality practices.

We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations). The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web pages and the quality of our service, and no personally identifiable information is shared with or sold to other organizations for commercial purposes, except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * It is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, by lawful request of public authorities and national security or law enforcement requirements, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Terms of Service, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if 15Five is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, 15Five will use reasonable efforts to notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Information gathering and usage

When you register for 15Five we ask for information such as your name, company name, email address, billing address, credit card information. Members who sign up for a free trial are not required to enter a credit card.

15Five uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research.

15Five may also use non-personally identifiable data submitted by Users to create and provide new services, features or content. For example, and without limitation, we may use data like employee pulse trends rates to publish interesting observations for informational or marketing purposes. 15Five will anonymize such data such that neither users nor Subscribing Organizations are identified.

15Five may internally perform statistical and other analysis on information we collect (including usage data, device data, referral data, and information from page tags) to analyze and measure user behavior and trends, to understand how people use our services, to monitor, troubleshoot and improve our services, and to create and provide new services, features or content.

When you access our Service by or through a mobile device, we may receive or collect and store unique identification numbers associated with your device or our mobile application (including, for example, a Unique Device Identifier (“UDID”), Unique ID for Advertisers (“IDFA”), Google Ad ID, or Windows Advertising ID), device type, model and manufacturer, and mobile device operating system brand and model.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Cookies are required to use the 15Five service.

We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to log-in to your 15Five after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

We may also collect analytics data, or use third-party analytics tools, to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service and to understand more about the demographics of our visitors. These tools collect information sent by your browser or mobile device, including the pages you visit, your use of third party applications, and other information that assists us in analyzing and improving the Service. Although we do our best to honor the privacy preferences of our visitors, we are not able to respond to Do Not Track signals from your browser at this time, as we believe that there is no consistent industry standard for how to respond to Do Not Track browser settings.

### Data storage

15Five uses third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run 15Five. Although 15Five owns the code, databases, and all rights to the 15Five application, you retain all rights to your data.

### Disclosure

15Five may disclose aggregated, anonymous, or anonymized data to third parties for market research, trend research, academic research, benchmarking, forecasting, or any other purpose. In all such instances, we will not disclose any identifiable information about you, your respondents, or your company. 15Five may also analyze your usage patterns and the usage patterns and respondents to improve or optimize our services. Consistent with this Privacy Policy, 15Five may also disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

### Online advertising and controlling cookies

We may permit third party online advertising networks to collect information about your use of our website over time so that they may play or display ads that may be relevant to your interests on other websites or apps. Typically, the information we share is provided through cookies or similar tracking technologies. The only way to completely “opt out” of the collection of any information through cookies or other tracking technology is to actively manage the settings on your browser or mobile device. Please refer to your browser’s or mobile device’s technical information for instructions on how to delete and disable cookies, and other tracking/recording tools. (To learn more about cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and related technologies, you may wish to visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org and/or the Network Advertising Initiative’s online resources, at http://www.networkadvertising.org). If you access our service on your mobile device, you may not be able to control tracking technologies through settings.

### Storage and transfer

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which 15Five or its subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction, and you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or any other country in which we or our parent, subsidiaries, affiliates or service providers maintain facilities and the use and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.

15Five, Inc. may provide Personal Data to Third Parties and vendors that act as agents, business partners, consultants, and contractors to perform tasks on behalf of and under our instructions such as technical support, client education, billing, analytics, and communication. Such Third Parties must agree to use such Personal Data only for the purposes for which they have been engaged by 15Five, Inc.

15Five, Inc. recognizes potential liability in cases of onward transfer to third parties. 15Five, Inc. will not transfer any personal information to a third-party without first ensuring that the third-party adheres to the Privacy Shield principles.

### Keeping information safe

15Five cares about the security of your information and uses commercially reasonable physical, technical and organizational measures designed to preserve the integrity and security of all information we collect and that we share with our service providers. However, no security system is impenetrable and we cannot guarantee the security of our systems 100%. In the event that any information under our control is compromised as a result of a breach of security, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and where appropriate, notify those individuals whose information may have been compromised and take other steps, in accordance with any applicable laws and regulations.

### Links to third-party websites and services

For your convenience, our website and Services may provide links to third-party websites or services that are not governed by this Privacy Policy. To the extent that any linked third-party websites or services you visit are not owned or controlled by 15Five, we are not responsible for those websites’ or services’ content or information practices. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of any site or service before providing any personal information.

### Privacy Shield

15Five, Inc. complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States.

15Five, Inc. complies with the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from Switzerland to the United States.

15Five, Inc. has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

15Five, Inc. is subject to investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, 15Five, Inc. commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact 15Five, Inc. at: [compliance@15five.com](mailto:compliance@15five.com)

15Five, Inc. has further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS (Judicial Arbitration and Mediation Services, Inc), an alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not addressed your complaint to your satisfaction, please contact or visit https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield for more information or to file a complaint. The services of JAMS (Judicial Arbitration and Mediation Services, Inc) are provided at no cost to you.

15Five, Inc. has further committed to cooperate with the panel established by the EU data protection authorities (DPAs) with regard to unresolved Privacy Shield complaints concerning human resources data transferred from the EU in the context of the employment relationship.

EU Persons may have the option to select binding arbitration under the Privacy Shield Panel for the resolution of your complaint under certain circumstances. For further information, please see the Privacy Shield website. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework at [https://www.privacyshield.gov](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).

EU Persons whose personal information is covered by this Privacy Shield Policy have the right to access the personal information that 15Five, Inc. maintains about them to correct, amend or delete such personal information if it is inaccurate or has been processed in violation of the Principles (except when the burden or expense of providing access, correction, amendment, or deletion would be disproportionate to the risks to the Data Subject’s privacy, or where the rights of persons other than the Data Subject would be violated). Requests for access, correction, amendment or deletion should be sent to: [compliance@15five.com](mailto:compliance@15five.com)

If Personal Data covered by this Privacy Shield Policy is to be used for a new purpose that is materially different from that for which the Personal Data was originally collected or subsequently authorized, or is to be disclosed to a non-agent third party, 15Five, Inc. will provide Data Subjects with an opportunity to choose whether to have their Personal Data so used or disclosed. To the extent required by the Privacy Shield Principles, 15Five, Inc. obtains opt-in consent for certain uses and disclosures of Sensitive Data.

### Children’s Privacy

15Five’s website and services are intended for use strictly by adults. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children under the age of 18. If we learn that any personal information has been collected from a child under 18, we will delete the information as soon as possible. If you believe that we might have collected information from a child under 18, please contact us at [privacy@15five.com].

### Changes

15Five may periodically update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your 15Five primary account holder account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

### Questions

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to privacy at 15five.com or by mail at:

15Five  
12 Gallagher Lane,  
San Francisco, CA 94103

These Terms were last modified on March 7, 2019.
